Hello everyone, welcome once again to
our fresh video of today. In
this video,
I am going to discuss with you
which stocks are listed in it and if you had
deposited some money in this mutual fund, what returns would you have seen in the
last three months, six months or one year.
And
in the last, I will discuss with you that what
we have is a return of
6.77 per cent. If we
talk about the 6-month return, then there is a return of 27.4 per cent in 6 months. If we talk about the one-year return, then there is a
return of 73.34 per cent in one year. And if we talk about the annual return, then the
annual return is 54.7 per cent.
We have just seen this,
first of all, its return. Now let us talk about
its NB. As of
today's date, its price of one NB
is 868 paise. If we talk about the rating, then
it has not got any kind of rating.
In this, you can make a minimum SIP amount.  The amount has been
kept at ₹5000000 and its fund size
is 3971 crores. Now let's talk about what returns you would have seen if
you had deposited some money in this mutual fund.
Before this, if you have
not yet opened your account in stocks and want to do so, then
I have given my referral link in the description of this video. If you
join through my referral link, then
you will get a cash bonus ranging from ₹500 to ₹1
and you will
not be charged any account opening charge nor is there any annual
maintenance charge. Let's talk about if you had
deposited ₹000 monthly in this mutual fund, then the money deposited in the third month would have been ₹
15000, you would have
got ₹1706. If we talk about 6 months, then
in 6 months your money would have been deposited ₹0000, you would have got ₹
22922. If we talk about 1 year, then in 1 year
your money would have been deposited ₹0000.  If you had made a
lump sum of ₹5000000, then in 3 months
your income would have been ₹1 lakh 2463, in 6 months
your income would have been ₹1 lakh
876 and in 1 year your income would have been ₹1 lakh
17340. Now if we look at the holdings, then the
total stocks listed in it are
77 stocks. If we
look at the top 10 and its sector wise, then the
first name that comes is Century Textile
and Industrial Limited, Consumer Steels
Construction, Cholo Mandalam Financial
Holding Limited, Financial Call India
Limited, Energy Godrej Industrial
Limited, Consumer
Steels Manda Corporation Limited,
Automobile, Union Bank of India
Financial Kilos Carr Oil Engine Limited is
under Capital Goods.
If we look at its holding analysis, then the equity pay is
92.8 and cash pay is 7.2. But now
if we look at this equity sector wise, then
Adarsh ​​Pay is 16.7, Consumer Steel 14.5,
Finance 13.6, Construction  11.8 Energy 10
Metals & Mining 99.7 Capital Goods 99.4
Services 88.8 and Health Care
5.5 Talking about its advance ratio,
its price to earnings ratio is
23.20 and its PV ratio is
3.17. If you want to invest your money in this mutual fund, then
through LSM you will have to invest a minimum of ₹000
and if you do SIP, then
you will have to do a minimum SIP of ₹55500.
Now we will talk about returns and ranking
and this is where you will understand
whether we should invest in this mutual fund
or not.
First of all, if we talk about returns, then if
seen from here, this
mutual fund has always given returns higher than its category. If we
look at the return rank category also, then it
ranks at number two in three months, at number two in six months and at
number two in one year, that is
This small cap mutual fund is
coming under the top category of return rank,
so you can invest in it,
if you have already invested then
you will continue your SIP or lump sum,
so let's talk about who is at number one here in the
category of return rank,
get some information about that too, that is
Quant Small Cap Fund, so if you are looking for a small
cap mutual fund today, then
I would tell you that apart from Quant,
your
small duty is
0.005, let's talk about its tax implications, the
tax implications will remain the same as in other
mutual funds, there is
no change, look at the fund house and investment
objects, so
this is an equity mutual fund which has been
launched,
then you will have to pay an exit load of 1 per cent here, so
today in this video I
discussed it with you